Bloom Southwest Jewish Archives Arizona Reference Files, ca. 1850-1998 (bulk 1870-1970)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Bloom Southwest Jewish Archives Arizona Reference files, ca. 1850-1998 (bulk 1870-1970)
SJA 004
Bloom Southwest Jewish Archives
This collection contains wide-ranging types of material regarding Jewish individuals and institutions in Arizona, principally southern Arizona. This material is especially reflective of the late-nineteenth century and the role of Jews in the Arizona Territory. The files consist primarily of newspaper clippings, scholarly and popular articles and excerpts, obituaries, auto-biographical reminiscences, copies of historical records, and correspondence. The bulk of the collection consists of secondary source material.
11 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Organization
The collection is arranged alphabetically by name or subject.
Scope and Content Note
Newspaper clippings, articles and excerpts, obituaries, autobiographical reminiscences, copies of historical records, and correspondence from late 19th and 20th century Arizona Jewish history.
Access Terms
Jews -- Arizona.
Pioneers -- Arizona.
Frontier and pioneer life -- Arizona.
Mineral industries -- Arizona -- History.
Synagogues -- Arizona.
Rabbis -- Arizona.
Commerce -- Arizona -- History.
Banks and banking -- Arizona -- History.
Retail trade -- Arizona -- History.
Jewish businesspeople -- Arizona -- History.
Arizona -- History -- 19th century.
Manuscript text.
Container List
- Aaron, Sam. (Box 1)
- Abend-Dulberg family. (Box 1)
- Abraham (surname). (Box 1)
- Abraham, Henry. (Box 1)
- Abraham, Jake. (Box 1)
- Abrahams, Bertram. (Box 1)
- Abrahams, Sidney, J. (Box 1)
- Abrams, Dr. Herbert. (Box 1)
- Abrams, Stanley. (Box 1)
- Abramson, Harry. (Box 1)
- Abramson, S. (Box 1)
- Ackerman, Abraham. (Box 1)
- Ackerman, Harry and family. (Box 1)
- Adler, Dr. Albert. (Box 1)
- All Peoples Synagogue (Tucson). (Box 1)
- Alpert, Dr. Joseph. (Box 1)
- Alter, Lewis J. (Box 1)
- Alter, Dr. Wilfred. (Box 1)
- Amado, Melissa. (Box 1)
- America - Israel Friendship League, Tucson Chapter/Jerusalem. (Box 1)
- American Friends of the Hebrew University (correspondence, publicity) - 2f. (Box 1)
- American Friends of the Hebrew University (finances) - 2f. (Box 1)
- American Friends of the Hebrew University (membership). (Box 1)
- American Friends of the Hebrew University (record of minutes). (Box 1)
- Amitim ("Jewish Peace Corps"). (Box 1)
- Amster, Leopold. (Box 1)
- Anne Frank Exhibit (advertisements). (Box 1)
- Anne Frank Exhibit (articles). (Box 1)
- Anne Frank Exhibit (educational outreach). (Box 1)
- Anne Frank Exhibit (organizers). (Box 1)
- Anne Frank Exhibit (public relations). (Box 1)
- Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, Arizona Chapter. (Box 1)
- Anti-Semitism in Arizona. (Box 1)
- Anti-Semitism in Tucson. (Box 1)
- Appel, Horace Hilary (Sr. and Jr.). (Box 1)
- Appel, Nathan B. (affidavits). (Box 1)
- Appel, Nathan B. (Arizona Pioneers' Historical Society). (Box 1)
- Appel, Nathan B.(biographical material). (Box 1)
- Appel, Nathan B. (book excerpts). (Box 1)
- Appel, Nathan B. (correspondence). (Box 1)
- Appel, Nathan B.(newspaper stories, 1850s-1890s; n.d.) - 2f. (Box 1)
- Appel, Nathan B. (obituaries). (Box 1)
- Appel, Nathan B. (research - Arizona Historical Society [Rabbi Floyd Fierman]). (Box 1)
- Appel, Rev. Elmer. (Box 1)
- "Argonaut Tales" (article). (Box 1)
- Arizona City. (Box 1)
- Arizona Historical Foundation. (Box 1)
- Arizona History (article - emigration). (Box 1)
- Arizona History (article - investments). (Box 1)
- Arizona History (book excerpt - History of Arizona, vol. 1). (Box 1)
- Arizona History (book excerpt - Our Southwest). (Box 1)
- Arizona History (timeline). (Box 1)
- Arizona Jewish Historical Society. (Box 1)
- Arizona Jewish Historical Society (Phoenix Chapter). (Box 1)
- Arizona Jewish Historical Society (Southern Arizona Chapter). (Box 1)
- Arizona Jewish Post (article about: "A Conspectus of Arizona's Pioneer Anglo-Jewish Newspaper"). (Box 1)
- Arizona and New Mexico History (article). (Box 1)
- Arizona (Pioneer) Historical Society (book excerpt). (Box 1)
- Arizona Quarterly Illustrated, 1880-81. (Box 1)
- Arizona Rangers (article). (Box 1)
- Aronson, John. (Box 1)
- Artzi, Sarah Tobin. (Box 1)
- Ash, Bruce. (Box 1)
- Asher Brothers' Powderhouse (articles). (Box 1)
- Asia, Daniel. (Box 1)
- Astronauts (Jewish - article). (Box 1)
- Atkinson, Sadie. (Box 1)
- Atlas, Louise C. (Box 1)
- Auerbach, Norman E. (Box 1)
- August, Harold. (Box 1)
- Bacal, Elizabeth. (Box 1)
- Backman, Felix. (Box 1)
- Backstein, Jacob. (Box 1)
- Baker, Donald. (Box 1)
- Banking in Arizona. (Box 1)
- Banta, Albert Franklin (excerpt from story by). (Box 1)
- Barkan family. (Box 1)
- Barnett, Aaron. (Box 1)
- Barr, Rev. Lawrence. (Box 1)
- Barth, Bernice. (Box 1)
- Barth, Isaac. (Box 1)
- Barth, Jacob. (Box 1)
- Barth, Maurice. (Box 1)
- Barth, Nathan. (Box 1)
- Barth, Solomon (biographical). (Box 1)
- Barth, Solomon (legal documents). (Box 1)
- Bashevkin, Albert. (Box 1)
- Baswitz, Louie and Henry. (Box 1)
- Baum, Kuno. (Box 1)
- Baum, Sarah. (Box 1)
- Becker, Rabbi Israel. (Box 1)
- Becker, Mark. (Box 1)
- Becker, Sylvia. (Box 1)
- Beigel, Alfred. (Box 1)
- Beigel, Allan. (Box 1)
- Beigel, Gisela. (Box 1)
- Beigel-Kaye, Joan. (Box 1)
- Beim, Mary. (Box 1)
- Bellman, Ben. (Box 1)
- Bellman, Lamar. (Box 1)
- Bellman, Melvina (nee Balk). (Box 1)
- Belzer, Suzanne. (Box 1)
- Ben-Asher, Susan (married name: Newton). (Box 1)
- Bendalin, Howard. (Box 1)
- Bendell, Herman. (Box 1)
- Benson, AZ (Jewish merchants in). (Box 1)
- Bensusan family. (Box 1)
- Beren family. (Box 1)
- Berger, J.M. (Box 1)
- Berger, Jeannie. (Box 1)
- Berger, Madeline Dreyfuss Heineman. (Box 1)
- Berger, Quincy Chaim. (Box 1)
- Bergman, Rabbi Moise. (Box 1)
- Bergman, Jacob. (Box 1)
- Berlowe, Herman. (Box 1)
- Berney, Leo. (Box 1)
- Bernstein, Beryl. (Box 1)
- Bernstein, Justice Charles. (Box 1)
- Bernstein, Dr. Dennis. (Box 1)
- Bersh, Victor. (Box 1)
- Bersu, Camilla. (Box 1)
- Beth El Congregation (Phoenix). (Box 1)
- Beth Emeth Congregation (Sun City West). (Box 1)
- Beth Joshua Congregation (Scottsdale). (Box 1)
- Bien-Willner, Ruben and Felissa. (Box 1)
- Bilgray (Rabbi Albert T.) Lectureship Steering Committee. (Box 1)
- Bilgray, Rabbi Albert T. (Box 1)
- Bisbee, AZ. (Box 1)
- Bisman, Rabbi Mark and Fredda. (Box 2)
- Blitzer, Professor Leon. (Box 2)
- Block, Ben. (Box 2)
- Block, Molly Handmaker. (Box 2)
- Bloom Brothers. (Box 2)
- Bloom, Clara Ferrin. (Box 2)
- Bloom, David Walter. (Box 2)
- Bloom, Naomi Gerstel. (Box 2)
- Bloom Southwest Jewish Archives - 3f. (Box 2)
- Bloom, Theodore F. (Box 2)
- Bloomfield, Suzanne. (Box 2)
- Blumberg, Abraham M. (Box 2)
- B'nai B'rith. (Box 2)
- B'nai B'rith Women. (Box 2)
- Bongarten, Harold. (Box 2)
- Bookbinder, Donald Gene. (Box 2)
- Bookman, Julius "Dooley". (Box 2)
- Boorstein, Mary. (Box 2)
- Boritzer, Regina. (Box 2)
- Bowie, AZ. (Box 2)
- Bracker, Robert. (Box 2)
- Bracker, Charles. (Box 2)
- Bracker, Joseph. (Box 2)
- Bracker, Pearl. (Box 2)
- Brandes, Raphael. (Box 2)
- Bravin, Lance. (Box 2)
- Breger, Bertha. (Box 2)
- Breger, Rabbi Marcus. (Box 2)
- Breger, Rabbi Marcus (correspondence). (Box 2)
- Breger, Rabbi Marcus (correspondence - University of Arizona). (Box 2)
- Breskin, "Aunt" Dolores. (Box 2)
- Breweries and Jewish Pioneers (book excerpt - Brewed in America: A History of Beer and Ale in the United States). (Box 2)
- "Brides for Brethren, 1854 - 1879" (article). (Box 2)
- Brock, Warren. (Box 2)
- Brook, Benjamin and Elizabeth. (Box 2)
- Brooks, "Al" Sumner. (Box 2)
- Brophy C. Frank. (Box 2)
- Brown, Jeanette. (Box 2)
- Brown, Morris J. (Box 2)
- Brown, Morris J. (Box 2)
- Burg, Sidney. (Box 2)
- Burnette, Ralph. (Box 2)
- Bush, Ruthann. (Box 2)
- Cabat, Erni and Rose. (Box 2)
- Calisher, M. (Box 2)
- Cantor, Judge Irwin. (Box 2)
- Capin, Dr. Donna. (Box 2)
- Capin, Esther. (Box 2)
- Capin family (clippings). (Box 2)
- Capin family (genealogy). (Box 2)
- Capin/Bracker families (genealogy). (Box 2)
- Capin, Fannie. (Box 2)
- Capin, Harlan. (Box 2)
- Capin, Helen. (Box 2)
- Capin, Hyman. (Box 2)
- Capin, Jacob (Jake). (Box 2)
- Capin, Leslie. (Box 2)
- Capin, Lillian. (Box 2)
- Capin, Philip. (Box 2)
- Capin, Richard. (Box 2)
- Capin, Samuel, 1877-1931. (Box 2)
- Capin, Samuel, 1903-68. (Box 2)
- Capin, Sylvia. (Box 2)
- Cattlemen (Jewish). (Box 2)
- Cauthorn, Robert S. - 2 f. (Box 2)
- Censuses of Arizona Territory (Jewish listings), 1860-1880. (Box 2)
- Cerf, Marian. (Box 2)
- Chambers, Winnie Emma. (Box 2)
- Chanen, Herman. (Box 2)
- Chanin, Abraham. (Box 2)
- Charleston, AZ. (Box 2)
- Charpentier, Harry ("Pepper"). (Box 2)
- Chernin, Bessie Capin. (Box 2)
- Chernin family. (Box 2)
- Chernin, Harry. (Box 2)
- Chesin, Ruth. (Box 2)
- "Chronicle" (newsletter of the Southern Arizona Chapter of the American Jewish Historical Society). (Box 2)
- Church Arson Prevention Act. (Box 2)
- Citron, Aaron L. (Box 2)
- Civil War (Arizona battles in). (Box 2)
- Clifton, AZ. (Box 2)
- Cochise County Historical and Archaeological Society. (Box 2)
- Cochise County (law enforcement). (Box 2)
- Cohen, Adeline R. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Charles E. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Harry. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Haskell. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Henry. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Janice E. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Marvin S. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Maurice. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Meyer. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Morris. (Box 2)
- Cohen, Dr. Sam. (Box 3)
- Cohen, Sarah W. (Box 3)
- Cohen, Woody. (Box 3)
- Cohn, Alfred A. (Box 3)
- Cohn, Rabbi Benjamin. (Box 3)
- Cohn, B[ernard?]. (Box 3)
- Cohn brothers. (Box 3)
- Cohn, David. (Box 3)
- Cohn, Elias and H.M. (Box 3)
- Cohn, I. (Box 3)
- Cohn, Joseph. (Box 3)
- Cohn, M.W. (Box 3)
- Cole, Beatrice. (Box 3)
- Coleman, Celia. (Box 3)
- "Colorado, New Mexico, Utah, Nevada, Wyoming, and Arizona Gazetteer and Business Directory, 1884-1885" (photocopy). (Box 3)
- Conferences (Jews in the Southwest United States). (Box 3)
- Congregation Anshei Israel (Tucson) - 3f. (Box 3)
- Congregation Beis Menachem (Phoenix). (Box 3)
- Congregation Bet Shalom (Tucson). (Box 3)
- Congregation Chaverim (Tucson). (Box 3)
- Congregation Chofetz Chayim (Tucson). (Box 3)
- Congregation Eshel Avraham (Tucson). (Box 3)
- Congregation Young Israel (Tucson). (Box 3)
- Consolidated National Bank (Tucson). (Box 3)
- Contracts and consignments (historical; photocopies). (Box 3)
- Cooper, Michael. (Box 3)
- Copeland, Isaac. (Box 3)
- Coppersmith, Senator Sam. (Box 3)
- Cornfield, Bernard. (Box 3)
- Cornfield, Matilda ("Tillie"). (Box 3)
- Costin, Max. (Box 3)
- Cranston, Jack. (Box 3)
- "Culture and Community: Artistic Encounters" (project of the National Foundation for Jewish Culture). (Box 3)
- Cunningham, George. (Box 3)
- Custer, Howard and Morton. (Box 3)
- Cyment, Dorothy. (Box 3)
- Danforth Chapel (Arizona State University). (Box 3)
- Darby, Dr. Richard. (Box 3)
- Davis, Betty Jane. (Box 3)
- Davis, Mayor Lewis. (Box 3)
- Davis Monthan Air Force Base (Tucson; Jewish activities; "The Shofar" - newsletter). (Box 3)
- Deitel, Saul and Rose. (Box 3)
- "Los Descendientes del Presidio de Tucson" (newsletter). (Box 3)
- Deutch, Sidney J. (Box 3)
- Deutsch, Sam. (Box 3)
- Dever, William. (Box 3)
- Diamond, Donald R. (Box 3)
- Diamond, Isaac. (Box 3)
- Diamond, Joseph. (Box 3)
- Diamond, Nathan. (Box 3)
- Dickstein family. (Box 3)
- Dickstein, Harold. (Box 3)
- Dickstein, Irwin. (Box 3)
- Dickstein, Dr. Stephen. (Box 3)
- Dietrich, Harvey. (Box 3)
- Dinnerstein, Leonard. (Box 3)
- Dinnerstein, Myra. (Box 3)
- Dobkin, Minnie. (Box 3)
- Doll, Peter. (Box 3)
- Donau, Alfred. (Box 3)
- Donau, Hugo. (Box 3)
- Donnadieu, Gabriel. (Box 3)
- Dorson, Sylvia. (Box 3)
- Dorson, William. (Box 3)
- Douglas, AZ. (Box 3)
- Douglas (AZ) Cemetery. (Box 3)
- Douglas Military Camp. (Box 3)
- Dow, Rabbi Ydel. (Box 3)
- Downing, Dimitri Y. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Albert. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Emanuel. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Esther. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Harry. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Herbert. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Jennie. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Lucille. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Mose. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Myra. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Philip. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Rosa Katzenstein. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Roy. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Sally Spaid. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Samuel H. - 2f. (Box 3)
- Drachman, Samuel H. (diary - photocopies). (Box 4)
- "The Drachmans of Arizona" (article - Floyd S. Fierman). (Box 4)
- Dreyer, Sam. (Box 4)
- Duckstein, Lucien. (Box 4)
- Dumes, Scott. (Box 4)
- Dumes, William. (Box 4)
- Dun and Bradstreet Mercantile Agency (reference book - 1908). (Box 4)
- Dunn, Seth. (Box 4)
- Dworin, Dr. Milton. (Box 4)
- Earp, Wyatt. (Box 4)
- Eber, Solly. (Box 4)
- Eckstein, Dr. Albert. (Box 4)
- Ehrenberg, Herman. (Box 4)
- Ehrlich, Dr. Joe. (Box 4)
- Eisenberg, Abe. (Box 4)
- Eisenberg, S. Harold. (Box 4)
- Elias, Jacob. (Box 4)
- Elkus, Irene. (Box 4)
- Ellis, N. (Box 4)
- Eloy, AZ. (Box 4)
- Emanuel, Abraham H. (Box 4)
- Ephraim, Leopold. (Box 4)
- Epstein, Harry. (Box 4)
- Erman family. (Box 4)
- Ettinger, Rowena. (Box 4)
- Evangelism from Christians (Jewish reactions to). (Box 4)
- Evans, Robert. (Box 4)
- Ezekiels, Al. (Box 4)
- Ezekiels, Louis. (Box 4)
- Ezekielville. (Box 4)
- Fairbank, AZ. (Box 4)
- Falkow, Cantor Maurice. (Box 4)
- Farming (Jews in). (Box 4)
- Feder, Bradley, H. (Box 4)
- Feig family. (Box 4)
- Feldman, Alther M. (Box 4)
- Feldman, Hank. (Box 4)
- Feldman, Henry. (Box 4)
- Feldman, Joesph. (Box 4)
- Feldman, Oded and Ina. (Box 4)
- Feldman, Stanley G. (Box 4)
- Feldman, Yosef. (Box 4)
- Fenster, George and Kitty (benefactors of the Fenster School). (Box 4)
- Fenton, Margie. (Box 4)
- Fenton, Norman. (Box 4)
- Ferdie, Moreen. (Box 4)
- Ferentz, Judd. (Box 4)
- Ferrin, Arthur H. (Box 4)
- Ferrin, Joseph. (Box 4)
- Ferrin, Therese Marx. (Box 4)
- Feyder, Leslie Newman. (Box 4)
- Fierman, Floyd. (Box 4)
- Fierst, Esther. (Box 4)
- Fine, Jack and Tillie. (Box 4)
- Fine, Sylvia Vogel. (Box 4)
- Fink, Richard. (Box 4)
- Finkelstein, Jack. (Box 4)
- Finkelstein, Rita. (Box 4)
- Fireman, Bert. (Box 4)
- Fischer, Adele. (Box 4)
- Fishman, Joesph. (Box 4)
- Fishman, Larry. (Box 4)
- Fleischman, Lawrence. (Box 4)
- Fleishman, Fannie Dreyfuss. (Box 4)
- Fleishman, Fred. (Box 4)
- Fleishman, Herman. (Box 4)
- Florsheim, William. (Box 4)
- Flyer, Anna. (Box 4)
- Fortman, Brian. (Box 4)
- Frank, Abraham. (Box 4)
- Frankl, Captain Robert A. (Box 4)
- Franklin, Abraham M. (Box 4)
- Franklin family. (Box 4)
- Franklin, Selim M. (Box 4)
- Franklin, Shirley Alter. (Box 4)
- Freedom Run (race against prejudice in Tucson). (Box 4)
- Freudenthal/Lesinsky/Solomon families. (Box 4)
- Fried, Mary L. (Box 4)
- Friedman, Bernard. (Box 4)
- Friedman, Charles. (Box 4)
- Friedman, Frank. (Box 4)
- Friedman, Harry. (Box 4)
- Friedman, Herman. (Box 4)
- Friedman, Leah and Sol. (Box 4)
- Friedman, Sam. (Box 4)
- Frohman, Elaine. (Box 4)
- Fruchthendler, Jacob C. (Box 4)
- Fruchthendler, Jean Abend. (Box 4)
- Fuchs, Morton. (Box 4)
- Funk family. (Box 4)
- Furst, Beth. (Box 4)
- Gaber, Pamela. (Box 4)
- "Galveston Plan" (settling of Jewish immigrants in the West). (Box 4)
- Ganz, Emil and Sylvan. (Box 4)
- Garber, Dick and Harriet. (Box 4)
- Garrard, John and Carol. (Box 4)
- Gelband, Claire. (Box 4)
- Geller, Milton. (Box 4)
- Gellman, Stuart. (Box 4)
- Gerst, Morris. (Box 4)
- Gibson, Robert. (Box 4)
- Giffords, Gifford ("Gif"). (Box 4)
- Gila City, AZ. (Box 4)
- Gilbert, Alice (SEE: Solmon/Goldberg). (Box 4)
- Ginsberg, Anna. (Box 4)
- Ginsburg, David and Helen. (Box 4)
- Ginsburg, Genevieve. (Box 4)
- Giss, Goldie. (Box 4)
- Giss, Harold C. (Box 4)
- Glassberg, Sharon. (Box 4)
- Globe, AZ. (Box 4)
- Glogoff, Stuart. (Box 4)
- Goetz, Richard H. (Box 4)
- Gold, Frank. (Box 4)
- Gold, Reuben. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Abe. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Arthur. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, David. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Emma V. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Eugene. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Joe. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Julius. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Louis. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Marcus. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Nathan. (Box 4)
- Goldbaum, Sarah. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Aaron. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Bernard A. (Box 4)
- Goldberg Brothers Clothing Store (Phoenix). (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Mrs. Carrie (wife of Aaron). (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Charles. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Chester Sr. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, David. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Ed. (Box 4)
- Goldberg family. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Hyman. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Isaac. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Marvin. (Box 4)
- Goldberg, Dr. Philip. (Box 4)
- Goldenberg, Lillian. (Box 4)
- Golden Eagle Brewery (Tombstone). (Box 4)
- Goldish, Matt. (Box 4)
- Goldman, Adolf. (Box 4)
- Goldman, Ben. (Box 4)
- Goldman, Bertha Feiler. (Box 4)
- Goldman Brothers (Phoenix). (Box 4)
- Goldman, Charles. (Box 4)
- Goldman, Elliot Sheldon. (Box 4)
- Goldman, Helen Toppel. (Box 4)
- Goldman, Irwin L. ("Buddy"). (Box 4)
- Goldman, Leo and Charles. (Box 4)
- Goldman, Maurice. (Box 4)
- Goldman, S. B. (Box 4)
- Goldschmidt, Adolph. (Box 4)
- Goldschmidt, Alfred J. and Louise. (Box 4)
- Goldschmidt, Leo. (Box 4)
- Goldsmith, Ben. (Box 4)
- Goldsmith, Grace. (Box 4)
- Goldstein, Brian. (Box 4)
- Goldstein, Dorothy. (Box 4)
- Goldstein, J. (business owner in Prescott, AZ). (Box 4)
- Goldstein, Judith. (Box 4)
- Goldstein, Lois. (Box 4)
- Goldtree, Estelle. (Box 4)
- Goldtree, Harriet. (Box 4)
- Goldtree, Isador. (Box 4)
- Goldtree, Joesph. (Box 4)
- Goldtree, Lillian. (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Baron (Barry, Sr.). (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Senator Barry (Barry, Jr.). (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Ben. (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Carrie. (Box 4)
- Goldwater family. (Box 4)
- Goldwater genealogy. (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Henry. (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Joesph. (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Julius. (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Michael. (Box 4)
- Goldwater, Morris. (Box 5)
- Goldwater, Sam. (Box 5)
- Goldwyn, Lillian Hurwitz. (Box 5)
- Goodman, A. (Box 5)
- Goodman, Edward. (Box 5)
- Goodman, Leon. (Box 5)
- Goodman, Mary. (Box 5)
- Goodman, Yetta. (Box 5)
- Gorbakovsky, Edward. (Box 5)
- Gordon, Edna. (Box 5)
- Gordon, William. (Box 5)
- Gottesman, Iris. (Box 5)
- Gotthelf, Isadore. (Box 5)
- Government (Jews in; book excerpt - Legislative History: Arizona 1864-1912). (Box 5)
- Government (Jews in). (Box 5)
- Grabb, Samuel. (Box 5)
- Graham County, AZ. (Box 5)
- Greenbaum, Alice. (Box 5)
- Greenbaum, Dr. Arnold. (Box 5)
- Greenberg, Bruce. (Box 5)
- Greenberg, George. (Box 5)
- Greenberg, Harold. (Box 5)
- Greenman, Rose. (Box 5)
- Green Valley, AZ. (Box 5)
- Greenwald, Samuel. (Box 5)
- Grossman, Lou. (Box 5)
- Grouskay, Aubrey. (Box 5)
- Grouskay family. (Box 5)
- Grunewald family. (Box 5)
- Gulf War. (Box 5)
- Gumbiner, Rabbi Joesph. (Box 5)
- Gunst, Ralph. (Box 5)
- Guralnick, Ralph. (Box 5)
- Guy, Dr. Donna. (Box 5)
- Haas, Brenda. (Box 5)
- Halper, Stacey. (Box 5)
- Hammer, Dr. Michael. (Box 5)
- Hammerschlag, Dr. Carl. (Box 5)
- Handmaker family (esp. Isadore H. ["Murf"]). (Box 5)
- Handmaker Home for the Aged (Tucson). (Box 5)
- Hartman, Norman and Francesca. (Box 5)
- Har Zion Congregation (Paradise Valley). (Box 5)
- Hebrew Benevolent Society (Tucson). (Box 5)
- "Heichal Baoranim" (newsletter - Phoenix). (Box 5)
- Heiman, Andrea. (Box 5)
- Heiman, Sandra R. (Box 5)
- Heineman, Samuel. (Box 5)
- Heineman, Simon. (Box 5)
- Heisler, Michael. (Box 5)
- Heller, Louis. (Box 5)
- Henderson, Abraham. (Box 5)
- Herberg, Lloyd. (Box 5)
- Herman, Betty Jane. (Box 5)
- Herman family. (Box 5)
- Herman, Maury. (Box 5)
- Hersh, Bianca. (Box 5)
- Herzberg, Dr. Benjamin. (Box 5)
- High Holy Days. (Box 5)
- Hillel (Arizona State University). (Box 5)
- Hillel (University of Arizona). (Box 5)
- Hirsch, Sarah S. (Box 5)
- Holocaust. (Box 5)
- Horn, Henry. (Box 5)
- Horwitz, Harry. (Box 5)
- Hyman, Julia. (Box 5)
- Ilitskey, Isadore. (Box 5)
- Immigration (Soviet Jews). (Box 5)
- Irwin, Alfred. (Box 5)
- Isaacson, Jacob. (Box 5)
- Isenstein, Bob. (Box 5)
- Iseral, Julia Schaffer. (Box 5)
- Jacobs family. (Box 5)
- Jacobs, Harold. (Box 5)
- Jacobs, Leon. (Box 5)
- Jacobs, Marion. (Box 5)
- Jacobs, Mark. (Box 5)
- Jacome family. (Box 5)
- Jastro, Henry. (Box 5)
- Jerome, AZ. (Box 5)
- Jewish calendar calculations. (Box 5)
- The Jewish Chronicle, 1841-1941 (excerpt). (Box 5)
- Jewish Community Foundation of Southern Arizona. (Box 5)
- Jewish Community Relations Council (Tucson). (Box 5)
- Jewish Family and Children's Service (Tucson). (Box 5)
- Jewish Federation of Southern Arizona. (Box 5)
- Jewish Historical Society of Southern Arizona. (Box 5)
- Jewish pioneer men in the West (articles). (Box 5)
- "Jewish Pioneers in Arizona" (article). (Box 5)
- "A Jewish Tourist's Guide" (excerpt). (Box 5)
- Jewish Web Sites (World Wide Web). (Box 5)
- The Jews in Arizona -- New Challenges. (Box 5)
- Jews in Chihuahua -- Appendix VI" (excerpt). (Box 5)
- "Jews of Arizona" (article - Freedman). (Box 5)
- "Jews of Arizona" (article - Rochlin). (Box 5)
- Joffe, Leonard. (Box 5)
- Joffe, Steve. (Box 5)
- Journalism (Jews in). (Box 5)
- Kahn, Belle. (Box 5)
- Kahn, Richard. (Box 5)
- Kaiserman, Jeffrey. (Box 5)
- Kalish family. (Box 5)
- Kane, Fan. (Box 5)
- Kaplan, Alexander. (Box 5)
- Kaplan, Helen. (Box 5)
- Kaplan, Irving D. (Box 5)
- Kaplan, Ruth. (Box 5)
- Kaplan, Sydney ("Duke"). (Box 5)
- Karon, Bruce A. (Box 5)
- Karp, Dr. Leonard R. (Box 5)
- Karsch, Carol and Daniel. (Box 5)
- Karz-Wagman, Rabbi Harley. (Box 5)
- Katcher, Fannie. (Box 5)
- Katz, Harold. (Box 5)
- Katz, Harry. (Box 5)
- Katz, Henry. (Box 5)
- Katz, Marcus. (Box 5)
- Katz, Ronald. (Box 5)
- Katzenstein, Albert. (Box 5)
- Katzenstein, Alma. (Box 5)
- Katzenstein, Frieda. (Box 5)
- Katzenstein, Sam. (Box 5)
- Kauffman, Davidson, Semmel, Inc. (Box 5)
- Kaufman, Frances. (Box 5)
- Kaufman, Harold. (Box 5)
- Kaufman, Henry. (Box 5)
- Kaufman, Judah. (Box 5)
- Kaufman, Ruth. (Box 5)
- Kaufman, Sam. (Box 5)
- Kaufman, Tave G. (Box 5)
- Kay, Morton. (Box 5)
- Kaye, Bobby. (Box 5)
- Kaye, Judy. (Box 5)
- Keane, Norman. (Box 5)
- Keller, Irving. (Box 5)
- Kellman, Herman. (Box 5)
- Kimmelman, Alex. (Box 5)
- King, Benjamin. (Box 5)
- Kingman Cemetery records (Kingman, AZ). (Box 5)
- Kipnis, Sam. (Box 5)
- Kippe, Mollie. (Box 5)
- Kivel Care Center (Phoenix). (Box 5)
- Kivel, Joesph K. (Box 5)
- Klein, Gerda Weissmann. (Box 5)
- Klein, H. W. (Box 5)
- Klein, S. (and Company). (Box 5)
- Kleiner, Dr. Stanley. (Box 5)
- Kleinerman, Ed. (Box 5)
- Kleinman, Julius. (Box 5)
- Kline family. (Box 5)
- Koffler, Dr. Henry. (Box 5)
- Koppell, Rabbi Bonnie. (Box 5)
- Korrick family. (Box 5)
- Koschland, Moses. (Box 5)
- Kozolchyk, Boris. (Box 5)
- Krasner, Oscar. (Box 5)
- Kraszynski, Maurice. (Box 5)
- Kritchevsky, Elise. (Box 5)
- Kroloff, Geraldine. (Box 5)
- Krueger, Rudi. (Box 5)
- Kruglick, Burt. (Box 5)
- Krupp, Dr. Leon. (Box 5)
- Ku Klux Klan. (Box 5)
- Kulanu (Tucson). (Box 5)
- Kurn, Samuel and Jane. (Box 5)
- Kustner, Jack and Dorothy. (Box 5)
- Labensart, Irving. (Box 5)
- Lamb, Urusla. (Box 5)
- Lamden, Richard. (Box 5)
- Lanceman, Bernard. (Box 5)
- Landers, Samuel. (Box 5)
- Landman, Rebecca. (Box 5)
- Landsberger, Louis. (Box 5)
- Langer, Rubin. (Box 5)
- Lantin, Max. (Box 5)
- Lappit, Leopold. (Box 5)
- Lasner, Anne. (Box 5)
- Lauber, Margot. (Box 5)
- Law (Jews in). (Box 5)
- Lazard, Alphonse. (Box 5)
- Lazarow, Pearl. (Box 5)
- Lazarus, P. (Box 5)
- Lebeau, Saul. (Box 5)
- Lederman, Amy Hirshberg. (Box 5)
- Lederman, Bernard. (Box 5)
- Lederman, Rose. (Box 5)
- Leeds, Leona J. (Box 5)
- Lefty, William (formerly Levkowitz). (Box 5)
- Lehman, Marshall. (Box 5)
- Lehman, Sylvia Gold. (Box 5)
- Lehrer, Cy. (Box 5)
- Lehrer, Lenoard. (Box 5)
- Leichman, Nathan. (Box 5)
- Leonard, Judith. (Box 5)
- Leonard, Wendy. (Box 5)
- Lesinsky, Henry and Charles. (Box 5)
- Lessner, Harold. (Box 5)
- Levanthal, B. (Box 5)
- Levi, Fortunato. (Box 5)